<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TicTacTwo</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="third_fragment_label">Third Fragment</string>
    <string name="fourth_fragment_label">Fourth Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="part_1">
        TicTacToe² is just like any other TicTacToe game but it’s got a bit of a twist.
        Your main board will have a bunch of boards inside of it.
        Player 1 (the player who goes first) will pick which inner board they wish to play in, and will then play somewhere in that board like regular TicTacToe.
    </string>
    <string name="part_2">

        Player 2, however, will be moved to a different board matching where Player 1 played.
        For example: if Player 1 chose the top left board but plays in the middle cell, Player 2 will be moved to the board on the middle.

    </string>
    <string name="part_3">
        Once a player wins a board, eg Player 1 with the top left board, the main board will now show an X (or an O, depending on the winner) where it used to be empty. This means that the entire board has been won by that player.
        If you direct a player to a board that has been claimed, that player gets free choice to pick any board of their choosing. For example, if Player 1 won the top left board with a move in the top left cell, the top left board is complete so Player 2 can’t play there. Instead they get to choose any of the other available boards to play.
        The game will continue in this way until someone has won a regular TicTacToe win in the main board.
    </string>
    <string name="part_4">
        Now, before the game begins, you can select the names you and your friend wish to play under and even the size of the board. A regular TicTacToe² game has a depth of 2 (one main board and one inner board) and a main board size of 3 (3x3 grid). This can be modified to the user’s desire, however you can’t have a board of size 0. But otherwise if you wish to play a three hour long TicTacToe game with a depth of 6 and a board size of 5, we can’t legally stop you.
    </string>
</resources>